datos = [
  {
  "pregunta":  "1. What is the supreme law of the land?", 
  "respuesta":  "The Constitution", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 01.mp3", 
  },
  {
  "pregunta":  "2. What does the Constitution do?", 
  "respuesta":  "Sets up the government. Defines the government. Protects basic rights of Americans", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 02.mp3", 
  },
  "pregunta": "3. The idea of self-government is in the first three words of the Constitution.. What are these words?"
  "respuesta":  "We the People", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 03.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "4. What is an amendment?", 
  "respuesta":  "A change (to the Constitution). An addition (to the Constitution)", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 04.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "5. What do we call the first ten amendments to the Constitution?", 
  "respuesta":  "The Bill of Rights", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 05.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "6. What is one right or freedom from the First Amendment?", 
  "respuesta":  "Speech. Religion. Assembly. Press. Petition the government", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 06.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "7. How many amendments does the Constitution have?", 
  "respuesta":  "twenty - seven(27)", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 07.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "8. What did the Declaration of Independence do?", 
  "respuesta":  "- announced our independence (from Great Britain). - declared our independence(from Great Britain). - said that the United States is free(from Great Britain)", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 08.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "9. What are two rights in the Declaration of Independence?", 
  "respuesta":  "- life. - liberty. - pursuit of happiness", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 09.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "10. What is freedom of religion?", 
  "respuesta":  "You can practice any religion, or not practice a religion.", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 10.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "11. What is the economic system in the United States?", 
  "respuesta":  "- capitalist economy. - market economy", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 11.mp3", 

  "pregunta": "12. What is the “rule of law”?", 
  "respuesta":  "- Everyone must follow the law.. - Leaders must obey the law.. - Government must obey the law.. - No one is above the law.", 
  "sonido":  "sounds/Track 12.mp3", 
]
    